原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     吃冰棒   小酸奶
翻译     TheWalkingNerd   Silence
校对     吃冰棒
时间轴     今  没有影子
后期     8T
总监     小酸奶
他举起手臂
he raised his arm
指着库柏问我
and pointed at Cooper and asked me...
你认为里面的是谁
Who do you think that is there?
妈的
Damn!
我都不记得了
I hadn't remembered that.
现在想起来真是有趣
Now, this is really something interesting to think about.
是的
Yes.
我现在也开始想起来了
I'm beginning to remember that too.
双峰镇警局
好了
Hey. All right.
火鸡肉和芝士
Turkey and cheese.
火腿和芝士
Ham and cheese.
烤牛肉和芝士
Roast beef and cheese.
还有纯芝士
And just cheese.
谁点纯芝士啊
Who ordered just cheese?
我点的
I did.
都是旧事了  查德
It's all old business, Chad,
早在你之前了
from long before your time.
你们要去哪
Where you guys going?
去山上
Up the mountain.
你被捕了  查德
And you are under arrest, Chad.
搞什么
What the fuck?
怎么回事
What's this all about?
你应该知道的
I think you know.
安迪  博比
Andy, Bobby,
带他去楼下
take him downstairs.
你在犯一个天大的错误
You're making a big mistake!
你犯了错  查德
You made the mistake, Chad.
我们已经监视了你好几个月
We've been watching you for months.
收走他的警徽  把他关起来
Take his badge, too, and lock him up.
你在犯一个天大的错误
You're making a big mistake.
闭嘴
Shut up.
这是你的烤牛肉和芝士
There's your roast beef and cheese.
博比
Bobby.
我们现在走的这里以前是有路的
This used to be the road, where we're walking.
我爸以前的监听站就从这里穿过去
My dad's listening post station was right through there.
现在全都没了
Nothing left of it now.
全都搬走了
Took everything away.
你父亲以前在那是做什么的  博比
And what all did your father do up there, Bobby?
我不知道
I don't know.
全都是高度机密
It was all top secret.
我小的时候  他带我进去过几次
Took me inside a couple times when I was little,
但我只记得
but all I remember is
里面有很多很多机器
lots and lots of machines.
但是他还是会带我来
He would take me here, though.
等等
Just a sec.
就是这个
This is it,
《杰克兔子宫殿》
Jackrabbit's Palace.
以前我们会坐在这
You know, we'd sit here and-and...
编一些荒诞的故事
make up great tall tales.
这里向东走大约231米
Two hundred and fifty-three yards due east.
我们得在口袋里放点土
And we have to put some soil in our pockets.
但愿这不是父亲的其中一个荒诞故事
Let's hope this is not one of your father's tall tales.
我也希望不是
I hope so too.
我觉得不是
I don't think so.
我们很快就会知道
We'll soon find out.
父亲的确和我说过
Father did tell me
没有他的陪同下  不要在这里徘徊
never wander around here without him.
走吧
Let's go.
她还活着
She's alive.
两点53分  各位
It's 2:53, fellas.
我是
消防员
有火吗
Got a light?
我们要把她救下山
We need to get her down the mountain.
她非常地重要
She's very important,
而且有人想杀死她
and there are people that want her dead.
她的身体没事
She's fine physically.
我们要把她放进小屋里  她就会安全了
We need to put her in a cell where she'll be safe.
好
Okay.
这事别告诉任何人
Don't tell anybody about this.
刚才我们在那里发生了什么事
What happened to us back there?
我不知道
I don't know.
发生了一些事
Something.
但是我完全不记得了
But I don't remember a thing.
我也不记得
Same with me.
双峰镇警局
但愿这睡衣合身
I hope these pajamas are okay.
自从那次那只狗在这失踪后
They've been in my locker
这睡衣一直放在我的柜子里
since the time that dog got lost in here.
睡衣很漂亮  露西
They're beautiful, Lucy.
你还记得那晚吗  安迪
Do you remember that night, Andy?
记得
Yes, I do.
蠢蛋
Idiots.
你就是个笑话  安迪
You're a joke, Andy!
你不是警察
You're no kind of cop!
你根本就不是警察
You're no kind of cop at all!
You're no kind of cop at all.
你是大坏人  查德
You're a very bad person, Chad.
让好警察蒙上了坏名声
Give good policemen a bad name.
好警察坏名声
Good policemen a bad name.
闭嘴  你个烂醉鬼
Shut up, you fucking drunk!
该死的  我说了闭嘴
God damn it, I said shut up!
闭嘴
Shut up!
你他妈有什么毛病
What the fuck is wrong with you?
简直是一群神经病
Fucking nuthouse.
我最好这么做
I better do that.
这些板条箱你要我怎么处理
What'd you want me to do with the crates?
就留在那吧
Just leave them.
我明早会盖上布
I'll throw the linens on them in the morning.
那样他们比较方便
It's easier for them that way.
来
There you go.
别紧张
Take it easy.
我们没事的
We're cool.
好的  吉米
Okay, Jimmy.
再送一趟货
We got one more delivery,
咱们就去酒馆
and then it's hit the Roadhouse.
今天谁演唱
Who's playing?
不知道
Don't know.
你想去看蕾妮在不在
You want to see if Renee will be there.
可能吧
Yeah, maybe.
但她是有夫之妇
But she's married.
我知道
I know.
你多大了  弗莱迪
How old are you, Freddie?
23岁
Going on 23.
我还记得23岁的感觉
I remember being 23.
今天是我生日
It's my birthday today.
真的吗
Is that right?
生日快乐  吉米
Well, happy birthday, Jimmy.
这可是大事
This is a real occasion.
你是真的不能脱下那玩意是吧
So you really can't take that thing off, huh?
没办法
Nah, I can't.
我不明白
I don't understand.
这是我身体的一部分
It's, uh, part of me.
医生曾经尝试将它拿下来  结果...
Doctor tried to take it off once, and...
我就流血了
I started bleeding.
你从哪弄来的
Where'd you get it?
这我不能说
I'm, uh, not supposed to tell.
今天我生日  弗莱迪  你得告诉我
It's my birthday, Freddie. You gotta tell me.
我不会说出去的
Come on, I'm not gonna tell anybody.
反正讲了你也不会相信
Eh, you ain't gonna believe me anyway.
所以你可以告诉我啊
So you may as well tell me.
弗莱迪  拜托嘛  告诉我
Freddie, come on, tell me the story.
拜托了
Come on.
这个嘛
Well...
我都告诉医生了
I told the doctor.
应该也可以告诉你吧
I, uh--I guess I can tell you.
看在今天是你生日的份上
And seeing as how it's your birthday.
当时我还住在家里
I was still living at home, see?
那是哪里
Where was that?
东边的伦敦镇
That would be London Town, East End.
大概六个月前
About six months ago,
某一晚  跟我的伙计们去完夜店后
after a night down at the pub with me mates,
我独自走回家
I'm walking home alone.
我抄捷径转入小巷时
I get this peculiar feeling
突然有股莫名奇妙的感觉
as I turn into this alley I use as a shortcut.
我恍然大悟我是在浪费生命  吉米
It strikes me that I'm wasting me life, Jimmy.
四处游荡
Hanging about,
夜夜流连夜店  饮酒作乐
hitting the pub every night, drinking,
我应该要帮助其他人的
when I should be helping people.
就在那一晚我有了这种感受
With this feeling in me on this particular night,
而我在小巷里看见高高的一堆箱子
I see in the alleyway a high stack of boxes,
我就跳进去
and I jumped,
就图个好玩
you know, like, for fun.
我跳进箱子堆
I jumped onto this high stack of boxes.
突然之间
And all of a sudden,
我被吸进了空中的巨大的漩涡隧道
I was sucked up into the vortex of this massive tunnel in the air.
接着我发觉
Next thing you know,
我已经浮在半空中
I'm floating in thin air,
某处的空中
way up somewhere,
如同虚空
like a void.
有个伙计在那儿
And this bloke's there.
他自称"消防员"
The Fireman's what he's called himself.
他对我说
And he says to me,
"去你公寓附近的五金店
"Go to the hardware store near your flat.
你会找到一排绿色的园艺用手套
And there you will find a rack of green rubber gardening gloves.
其中有一包已经开封
One package will already be open,
里面只有一只右手的手套
with only a right-handed glove inside.
买下那一包
Purchase that package
将手套戴在你的右手
and place the glove on your right hand.
你的右手就会拥有打桩机一般的
Your right hand will then possess the power
巨大力量"
of an enormous pile driver."
砰一声
Poof.
我回到了我的房间
And I'm back in me room,
醒来已是隔天早上
waking up the next morning.
我起身下床
I got up, got out of bed.
梳头发
Dragged a comb across me head.
下楼  喝了一杯
And I went downstairs and had a cup.
不  这些是玩笑话
No. Just kidding about that part.
于是我去了转角的五金店
So I pop round the corner to the hardware store,
找到那一排手套
find the rack of gloves.
想当然
And, sure enough,
有一包已开封的手套  里面只剩右手
there's the open package with the one right hand.
我走去柜台
Off I go to the counter,
拿商品给店员结账
lay down the package for the clerk,
他说
and he says,
"我不能卖你这一副
"I can't sell you that one.
你得购买未开封的"
You have to buy one that hasn't been opened."
我说  "没事  我就要这副"
So I say, "That's all right. I want this one."
他说  "我不能卖你这一副"
He says, "I can't sell you that one."
我说  "听着  伙计
I says, "Listen, mate.
我只想买单只手套
I want to buy just the one glove,
我会付你一副的钱"
and I will pay you full price."
"不行  这袋已经开封
"No, it's already been opened.
我不能卖给你"
I can't sell it to ya."
在我老家呢
Now, where I come from,
我们管这种傻逼叫"死脑筋"
we call a bloke like this a "Jobsworth."
这种人喜欢
That is a person who delights in acting
阻挠别人或是拒绝配合
in an obstructive or otherwise unhelpful manner,
说什么"这我办不到
as in, "I can't do that.
超出我的工作权限了"
It's more than my job's worth."
所以我和死脑筋先生说
So I says to Mr. Jobsworth,
"听着  我要买这个手套"
"Listen, I'm buying this glove."
我就把我的钱放在柜台上往门外走
And I put me bees on the counter and walk towards the door.
死脑筋追在我后面  像一只猎豹
Well, Jobsworth leaps after me like a possessed puma,
大喊着我不能买已经开封的
screaming that I can't have the glove from the package
包裹中的手套
which has already been opened.
我冲出门  跑到路上
I bolt out the door, hit the cobbles,
想把死脑筋先生甩在身后
hoping to leave Mr. Jobsworth in the dust,
一边跑一边把手套戴在了手上
slipping the glove on while I go.
于是我的脚步稍微放缓了
Then he slows me down a mite.
然后突然间
And before you know it,
死脑筋先生猛地绊了我一下
Jobsworth puts a tackle on me worthy of a red card
我狠狠地摔在地上
and sends me skidding on the field.
我下意识地自卫
On instinct, to defend myself,
用我戴着绿手套的手揍了他一拳
I popped Jobsworth one in the loaf with me green glove.
我听到一声脆响  然后...
I hear a crack, and...
他的脑袋歪在一边  仿佛想说点什么
by the way his head's tilting and him trying to talk...
我怕我打断了他的脖子
...I fear I've snapped his Gregory.
然后
And then,
那一瞬间
in that moment,
我记起来那个飘在空中的东西还和我说过
I remember something else that bloke up in the sky told me.
"你戴上手套后
"Once you've got the glove on,
就去美国
go to Twin Peaks, Washington,
华盛顿州的双峰镇
United States of America.
在那里
And there,
你会找到你的命运"
you will find your destiny."
所以我就来了  吉米
So here I am, Jimmy,
在你的生日
on your birthday.
祝你长命百岁
Many happy returns.
谢谢你  弗莱迪  这个故事很不错
Thank you, Freddie. That's a great story.
不客气  先生
The pleasure's all mine, sir.
为什么选中你
Why you?
我是说你觉得消防员为什么选中你
I mean, why do you think the Fireman picked you?
这个问题不错
Well, that's a good question.
我也问过我自己  我说
I asked him myself, I said,
"为什么是我"
"Why me?"
他说
And he said,
"为什么不能是你"
"Why not you?"
然后我就去买机票飞到这里
And when I went to buy me ticket to fly over here,
他们告诉我我已经有机票了
they told me I already had a ticket.
别忘了
Don't forget.
我们得去检查锅炉
We're supposed to check the furnace.
嗯  你在这里等货
Yeah. You wait for the delivery.
别忘了在发票上签名
Don't forget to sign the invoice.
我去检查锅炉
I'm gonna go check the furnaces.
麋鹿九点酒吧
一杯血腥玛丽
Bloody Mary.
马上来
Coming up.
谢谢
Thanks.
你今晚一人独饮吗
You drinking all alone tonight?
别多管闲事
Mind your own business,
谢谢
please.
这样说可不礼貌
That's not very polite.
我本来就没打算有礼貌
It wasn't meant to be polite.
你能坐回
Would you sit back
你原来的位置吗
where you were,
谢谢
please?
我想做哪儿就坐哪儿
I'll sit wherever I want.
这是个自由的国家
It's a free country.
这是个自由的国妓啊
It's a free cunt-ry.
也许你是个女同
Maybe you're one of them bull dykes.
没错
Yeah.
我想了想
Come to think of it,
你看上去的确像女同性恋
you look kind of like a bull dyke lesbo.
你喜欢吃逼  是吧
You like to eat cunt, huh?
我会吃你
I'll eat you.
什么
What?
做梦去吧  你这贱人
Like hell you will, you miserable bitch.
我会把你这对同性恋奶子扯下来
I'll fucking pull your little lesbo titties off.
你真的想来挑事情吗
Do you really want to fuck with this?
搞什么  怎么回事
What the hell? What happened?
他突然倒下了  我不知道
He just fell over. I don't know.
怎么回事  他大半个脖子不见了
What, with half his neck missing?
该死
Damn.
这跟你有关系吗
You have something to do with this?
什么  你都看到我了
What? You-you saw me.
我就坐在这里喝酒
I was just sitting here, having my drink.
亲爱的
Honey!
快报警
Call 911!
酒吧里死人了
We got a dead one at the bar.
等警察来了再说
We'll see about this.
是啊
Yeah.
这真是个谜
Sure is a mystery, huh?
枪炮酒吧
那是因为你一直在精神病院里
That's because you're hanging out at the nuthouse.
我没有
I'm not.
在那里嗑嗨了
Getting high in there.
胡说  我没有
Bullshit. I'm not.
我在自己房间嗑嗨了
I'm getting high in my room.
在我自己房间里上天
Flying in my own room.
别去那个疯狂的地方
Just don't go in that nut place.
去你的  谁说我会去
Fuck you. Who said I would anyway?
毛衣不错
Nice sweater.
从哪儿偷来的
Where'd you lift that?
那是宝拉的
It's Paula's.
很不错
It's nice.
你最近见过比利吗
Have you seen Billy?
没有  好几天没见过了
No, not for a couple of days.
听说你是最后一个见到比利的人
I heard you were the last person to see Billy.
太可怕了
It was so fucking scary.
他当时跟我和我妈妈一起在厨房里
He was in the kitchen with me and my mom.
我叔叔应该也在
Think my uncle was there.
我不确定
I'm not sure, um...
然后我们看到比利在窗外
You know, at the window, we see Billy.
他跳过了篱笆  两米高的篱笆
He's jumped over a fence, a six-foot fence,
跳到我们的后院
lands in our backyard.
然后跟疯了似的冲向后门
He comes running like crazy to the back door.
我确定他从窗户里看到了我
And I can tell he sees me through the window.
他的眼神很奇怪
And he had this look in his eyes.
他撞开了后门
Comes slamming in the back,
闯进了厨房
stumbles in the kitchen.
我开始尖叫  我觉得我妈妈也在尖叫
I start screaming, and I think my mom screamed too.
他的鼻子和嘴巴都在往外冒鲜血
And there was blood coming out his nose and mouth.
然后他就把自己的脑袋伸进水槽里
And he goes and hangs his head in the sink.
血和瀑布一样流下来
Blood's just gushing like a waterfall.
他转头看向我们
And he turns and looks at us,
眼神很奇怪  全都是血
real strange and all bloody.
然后他又从后门冲了出去
And then he bolts out the back again.
我们一脸"怎么回事"
We're like, "What?"
你没有告诉过任何人吗
And you didn't tell anyone?
我们...我们不知道该怎么办
We-we just didn't know what to do.
我们不知道他到底怎么了
I mean, we didn't know what the hell was going on with him.
我知道我妈妈和他有一腿
And I know my mom and him had a thing.
什么  真的吗
What? Really?
是的
Yeah.
至少最近还有关系
Up until pretty recent, at least.
我是说我经常能听到风言风语
I mean, I just caught wind of it from time to time.
每次提到他的名字  都会露出意味深长的微笑
The smile in her face whenever his name came up.
你妈妈叫什么
What's your mom's name?
蒂娜
It's Tina.
他就这么又跑了出去
Then he just ran out again?
是啊  就像
Yeah, just, like,
他就在我们厨房待了十几秒
he was in our kitchen for maybe, like, ten seconds,
然后他就跑了  很快  很疯狂
and then he just took off, real fast and crazy.
然后  我们看到地上全是血
And after, we see all the blood on the floor
墙上也有一些
and some on the wall.
我和我妈妈花了好久
Took a while to clean it up,
才清理干净
me and my mom.
我记不清我叔叔在不在了
I don't remember if my uncle was there.
女士们先生们  欢迎丽斯上台表演
Ladies and gentlemen, the Roadhouse is proud to welcome Lissie!
*你会在那里*
*Are you out there*
*消除我的恐惧吗*
*To take away my fear? ♪
*我还没有丧失*
*I haven't lost*
*我的希望*
*My hope*
*尽管我离家*
*Even though I am so far*
*那么遥远*
*From my home*
*我宛如站在悬崖边缘*
*I've been living life on the edge*
*往前一步便是深渊*
*Slip and fall if I take one more step*
*虽说人多势也众*
*There's safety in numbers, I guess*
*但我独自奔跑在旷野  冲向西部*
*But I'm going rogue in the wild, wild west*
*冲向西部  冲向西部*
*Wild, wild west, wild, wild west*
*西部  西部*
*Wild, wild*
*我站在*
*From where*
*这个地方*
*I stand*
*你来自*
*There's a world*
*那个世界*
*Where you can*
*你失去的一切*
*All that you lost*
*都能夺回*
*You get back*
*你想要的*
*And all*
*一切*
*That you want*
*都能拥有*
*You can have*
*我宛如站在悬崖边缘*
*I've been living life on the edge*
*往前一步便是深渊*
*Slip and fall if I take one more step*
*虽说人多势也众*
*There's safety in numbers, I guess*
*但我独自奔跑在旷野  冲向西部*
*But I'm going rogue in the wild, wild west*
*冲向西部  冲向西部*
*Wild, wild west, wild, wild west*
*西部  西部*
*Wild, wild*
*我在月光下*
*I've been dancing*
*起舞*
*In the moonlight*
*我在火光中*
*I've been laughing*
*大笑*
*With the firelight*
*生存*
*Living*
*我一直在付出*
*I've been giving*
*我在火光中*
*I've been living*
*生存*
*With the firelight*
*我会没事  我会没事*
*I'll be fine, fine, I'll be fine, fine*
*我会*
*I'll be*
*没事*
*Fine*
*我宛如站在悬崖边缘*
*I've been living life on the edge*
*如果我跌落  谁会接住我*
*If I fall, who's gonna catch me?*
*虽说人多势也众*
*There's safety in numbers, I guess*
*但我独自奔跑在旷野  冲向西部*
*But I'm going rogue in the wild, wild west*
*我在月光下*
*I've been dancing*
*起舞*
*In the moonlight*
*我在火光中*
*I've been laughing*
*大笑*
*With the firelight*
*生存*
*Living*
*我在火光中*
*I've been living*
*我一直在付出*
*I've been giving*
*生存*
*With the firelight*
*我会没事  我会没事*
*I'll be fine, fine, I'll be fine, fine*
*我会没事*
*I'll be fine, fine*
*我会没事  我会没事*
*I'll be fine, fine, I'll be fine, fine*
*我会没事*
*I'll be fine, fine*